= kisskh.club =
[Disclaimer: Characters, locations,
and all depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
send in the guards, please.
There's a stalking sasaeng in here.
Just focus on your studies, guys.
Mon and I will handle this.
You wanna...
try auditioning for this?
[Casting Call]
Or you can't handle the truth I said?
Terrible.
What now?
Do you want me to tell everyone
who you really are?
Why are you here?
I'm sorry.
You feel better now?
Cher called.
Shit, you made the cut?!
[Two years ago]
Uh, hello.
My name is Nopphanat Wongwiboon.
You can put the name tag
on your shirt and wait inside.
[Nine]
Oh!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Thank... Thank...
Thank you.
Right...
I'm sorry about that.
Excuse me,
please make way.
Uh...
Are you Thee's fan?
I was hired to take photos.
Right.
Well, then...
please be careful.
Given how crowded it is,
another accident could happen.
Good thing you weren't hurt.
Thank you, and...
I'm sorry.
You're fine. This is all on me.
We're chill.
He looks incredibly striking.
You know,
I wanna be just like him.
But as of right now...
I'm trying.
One day, I'm going to be just like him.
When that day arrives,
and we come across each other again...
please...
take some nice photos of me.
Good luck.
I'm sure you can do it.
Thank you.
Then, excuse me. I'm heading inside.
Okay.
Oh!
Nice to meet you.
Take care.
Alright.
I regularly took on
photography work for artists,
but never once was I
particularly interested in anyone.
Then came...
the day I first met Nine.
I became a complete fanboy.
[#AuditionForTheBetLove's]
[Only focusing on TheeJuno, not listening
to anyone who says otherwise]
[I love Juno so much, so emotional since Day 1;
he's now the lead couple]
[This new chemistry
of ThirdNine is insane]
[We're getting TheeJuno as the main leads;
announce the ticket sale for EP1 now]
[ThirdNine is perfect,
and their chemistry is so good]
[It's like they walked straight out
of the novel; as its fan, I'm in tears]
[I wanna watch it already, go ahead
with the ceremony and start filming]
[Waiting for the pilot and the full version,
stanning ThirdNine from now on]
[Company, rest assured, the sponsors
are pouring in, so please hurry and make it]
[This company respects the novel, looking
forward to it; great cast, praying for a good plot]
[Hi!! I'm Nine. I'm auditioning
for a part in 'The Bet Love's' today;
please root for me]
[Following]
"Nine.nw..."
In my life, I've never thought
[Following]
I'd fanboy over anyone this seriously.
But how could I resist?
Look at Nine.
He's handsome, friendly,
and nice.
♫Though I once yearned for it♫
Are you singing
or just making up words?
Were you joking about liking him?
I like him for real.
Better look at Pink.
She looks even cuter in real life.
- She acts with...
- Yeah, yeah, whatever.
At first, I wondered
whether or not it was weird
liking an artist so much
that I went to events just to see them.
But not at all,
the more I got to know him,
the more I saw that
he didn't just have looks to offer,
but also a dream
and a passion.
And for that, I became
even more passionate about him.
When I first joined
the entertainment industry,
I went to many auditions.
Anywhere that was open
for newcomers, I was there.
One time, I auditioned three days in a row.
I took the Skytrain
just for this one sentence,
"Hello, my name is Nine,"
and then I went back home.
Yeah.
For anyone who's tired,
I'm rooting for you all.
You've got this.
Today might not be your day, but...
eventually,
it will be.
It's gonna come one day.
But on second thought,
no matter what people say,
I'm not bothering anyone.
Life is short.
Knock yourself out.
Even if I gush over someone 24/7,
it's not anyone else's business,
is it?
Wan, Wan!
ThirdNine is here!
Come quick!
- Let me see!
- Look!
[Love Suspect]
Play,
take a look at this.
What are we gonna do?
The side couple is everything!
Third acting is insane.
I'm choosing him as my bias.
True!
I think Nine does it better, though.
Ugh! Stop right there.
We can praise our biases
without comparing
them to anyone else's.
Right,
but Nine, though...
He's the best!
He's cute,
pretty, handsome,
majestic, and charming.
He's a freaking genius
and a complete all-rounder.
How can someone
be this fabulous?!
Jeez...
I can't even find words
to properly praise him.
My baby boy is also the best!
Who is your baby boy?
Third is!
Huh?!
He's older than you, girl.
Don't act so grown up!
What?!
I know.
Older or not, I can still be his mommy.
Even eighth graders
can join the mommy club.
It's all about free will!
What?!
[Directed by: Nathawat Piyanonpong]
This company
just loves abrupt endings.
It's on you for babbling so much!
Ugh, you wouldn't stop beefing with me!
And we'll have to wait forever.
I remember what Nine told me
the first day we met,
so I take beautiful photos
of him at every event.
But on top of that...
[Username: @1tonine_]
[1TONINE]
[Only for Nine Nopphanat]
[1,895 followers]
This...
is the life of a fanboy.
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
[Mr. Fanboy Series]
[Episode 2: "A Whole New World"]
Guys...
I'm gonna be close to Nine.
Sheesh...
Jeez, brother.
You're playing the antagonist.
Being close sounds more like
you're fighting with each other.
Wan's gonna look so stoked
when he gets punched in the face.
He's even over the moon
while eating dog food.
Ugh!
Want, stop it!
Get a grip!
So now that you're part of the series,
are you getting paid right away?
I have no clue.
I have to wait
until they give me more details.
You've gotta get it straight, man.
Yeah, also...
don't tell anyone you're Nine's fan.
I think I'm gonna tell them all.
Don't be ridiculous, sweetie!
You were both gonna get
taken away at that lineup event.
It was one big misunderstanding!
Sure!
If they find out,
they'll chew your ass off
for being a reformed sasaeng.
Is it so wrong that I'm his fan?
Besides,
is there not a single fan of an artist
working in the industry?
There is,
but you raised hell last time.
Shit! She's calling once again.
Are they canceling on you?
"Canceling," my ass.
Hello?
Are you canceling on me?
What are you talking about, sweetie?
Are you free today?
I want to invite you to the company.
Right.
Do you want me to go to the company today?
Go ahead
so you can discuss the pay.
Discuss what, sweetie?
Oh, uh...
Right...
No, that was nothing.
Sure thing.
I'll be coming in today.
Mm,
I'll forward you the location.
Yes, ma'am.
Wan!
Hello, Cher.
Let's go.
Straighten your back.
Yeah, all that slouching for what?
Oh, sweetie, it's okay.
Come on.
Welcome to 'Our House'!
This is the place...
where everyone's dream comes true!
Oh, Cher?
Hi, there.
Oh, Boom.
Haven't left for the flight?
What time?
Mm,
it's just what famous dudes do.
That wasn't the question.
The real answer is, I don't know.
Just getting through
each day in the company's van.
Mm, come on now.
You're blowing up,
so just bear with it.
Not everyone
gets to attend a fashion week overseas.
Yeah...
I know, I know, I know.
Then, this time,
sashay down there
and crush it all,
just not into a pole like last time.
We were all embarrassed back then.
Jeez, girl!
That's called...
"Out...
standing."
No one was brave enough to pull it.
It's one-of-a-kind
and sure is unprecedented.
Alright, I'm gonna do something so viral
that the whole world sees.
Rest assured.
This...
is what you call "famous."
Fabulous.
Maybe go for something else...
That'd be great, yeah?
So, where are you flying to this time?
I'm flying to Korea.
Though...
Paris is right around the corner.
Mm...
Oh, and...
Who do we have here?
Enjoying the conversation, huh?
Hello.
Hi.
Come on. I'm gonna take him to see Wut.
Mm-hm.
Good luck, boy.
One day,
you'll be as famous...
as me!
So famous that you wanna retire!
Woo!
Let's go. Come on.
See ya.
Compared to the series...
he seems different in real life, huh?
Mm,
because this is real life.
What you just witnessed...
was a real person.
It gets even more real from here.
You'll get it after some time.
Come on,
let's go see Wut.
- Hello.
- Come take a seat.
Hi.
Take a seat.
Tell me your personal background
in detail.
Right.
I'm...
Wan, Ashawin Kosonkasem,
21 years old.
I'm a senior in my second semester,
majoring in Public Relations
in the Communication Arts program.
I have one sister.
I'm from Ayutthaya.
My parents run a boat noodle shop.
In high school,
I came to study in Bangkok.
I'm living in my relative's condo
with my little sister.
Okay.
From now on,
our schedule will be absolutely packed,
starting today.
You're changing your look,
doing a fitting,
and filming the series.
Before the series, we're filming the pilot
and attending events.
As for the filming,
it comes to around 50 cues per series,
so you have to manage your time properly.
And if work starts flooding in,
I'd suggest you drop the semester,
even though this is your last one.
Trust me. It's gonna be worth it.
Alright.
So do you have any talent
or something you're an expert at?
I can play the guitar.
I can also sing a little.
However...
I don't know how to dance at all.
For whatever skills you already have,
take more classes to improve them.
As for those you don't have,
you'll need to work on them,
like dancing.
Sometimes, you need to attend events
or, like, fan-meeting stages.
You have to crush the performance
so as not to embarrass yourself.
Look at NuNew, for example.
That...
is the ideal bottom you have to become.
Alright.
Come on now.
Sign the contract.
Uh...
I do have a question.
Hm?
So...
If I sign,
could I work part-time jobs
or take on extra gigs?
No,
I don't think that's appropriate.
Then...
I'd rather not sign
because...
I'm not planning to become a celebrity.
I just want to earn money.
What's going on in your life?
My mom fell for a call-center scam,
so my family is in debt.
I have to help them make money.
And...
those jobs I take on
are my main income.
If you won't allow it,
I won't sign the contract.
How much do you owe?
500,000 baht.
Fine!
But I'm not letting you take on
photography gigs like before.
I'll cover that 500,000 debt of yours.
On one condition:
whatever you earn from now on,
half of your 70% share will be deducted
to pay the company back.
As for the rest, it's yours to keep.
This goes until you pay off the 500,000.
After that,
it's the normal 70:30 ratio.
But if you breach the contract,
you will be fined
2 million baht by the company.
Do we have a deal?
Yes, we have a deal.
Uh...
Then...
Please go ahead and transfer it.
I'll...
sign it right away.
Look at all that energy
compared to all that pondering earlier.
Sorry, sweetie.
I'll go ahead and modify the contract.
Make sure you write clear clauses.
Of course, gotta scan my face.
Well, you didn't remind me to get Botox.
My old face was like...
Mm.
It went through.
[Ashawin Kosonkasem]
[Artist]
Okay.
Welcome to...
'Our House.'
Alright.
Cue slogan.
"Where every dream comes true!"
Renji.
Oh?
This is Wan, our new boy.
Hello, Wan.
I'm Ren.
Hm?
Oh, not just Ren.
I'm Renji.
I'm not so used to the new name.
Uh...
Well...
Do I also have to change my name?
Do you want to?
Wanwoon.
Wankim.
Two-syllable names are so on trend.
Uh...
I think...
I'll sit this one out.
Okay.
From now on, I will take care of you two.
Tell me if you need anything.
Don't hesitate.
Roger that.
Wan?
Though...
we still need
to be considerate, right?
Because I...
am only human.
Absolutely...
Both of you, listen to me.
In this industry,
if you don't kill it,
you're dead.
If you don't get fierce,
you flop.
Therefore, both of you
will take an etiquette and poise course
and speech classes.
More importantly,
you're visiting a beauty clinic
because your faces make you money.
I'll get you some consultations, sweeties.
But I already have my go-to clinic.
Don't worry about it.
Okay,
Wan, any questions?
So, like...
Who will take care of the cost?
The company will.
Then, I'm willing to do anything!
Okay.
Lastly,
listen carefully and take it to heart.
So long as you're not in a private room,
no matter the situation,
do not frown,
make faces,
or look sullen.
You have to smile.
Are you done?
Uh, I have to go golfing with my friends.
Excuse me.
Bye.
See ya.
Uh, hey...
Oh.
It's gotta be a yes now, huh?
Then, I'll...
Hey, wait!
Didn't Wut tell you
what you've gotta do?
You have to start at this second.
Come on, it's makeover time!
But Renji...
He's already got one
since before the audition.
It's just... you now
who needs immediate help.
Let's go.
Go, go, go.
Walk up those stairs.
Everyone,
he's here.
Is this really a good idea, Cher?
Let's see.
Your hair...
[Wan]
Let me just say,
my makeup changed the game.
The makeup serves the face.
No, the hair does.
And my outfit serves that hair!
How about we break this team up?
Just kidding, bestie.
It was a joke, yeah?
Cher,
this boy
looks like he's gonna blow up.
Don't forget us then.
My boy here is ready to crash 'em.
Right, okay.
We're all done, sweetie.
Come on, we still have
to sign you up for the classes.
[CREWAVE]
All done.
I'll get it taken care of nicely.
Thank you very much.
Cher,
I have to be in all these classes?
That's right.
Singing, acting, dancing,
you've gotta ace them all,
just in case...
you'll have your own single in the future.
Releasing a single, too?
Mm.
I can't even get past acting yet.
Come on, just take the classes
now that you have the chance.
Hello, Cher.
Hello, Tawan.
Oh.
Hi, Third.
I'll get the room ready.
Congrats
on making the cut with a fluke.
Can't you really just walk past?
No...
Third,
your bag.
Alright.
Call me when you're done.
Wan,
let's go.
I'm sorry.
You're Wan, the boy who made the cut
for 'The Deep Between Us'
Yes…
Congratulations.
Thank you...
Lady.
Come on, Wan.
Go home and rest. I'm taking you
to the clinic tomorrow
because I've got you an appointment.
That boy...
looks familiar
and sounds familiar,
doesn't he?
Not just familiar,
that's the exact guy.
Whoa...
That's not right.
Why not?
He made the cut fair and square.
[Gangnam]
Hello.
I brought our new boy here
to get to know you guys.
Hello, I'm Wan.
Hello.
You're so adorable in person.
Please get him
a consultation with the physician
since he's never
gotten treatments done before.
Anyway, please adore him.
Hello, Ms. Sunny.
We have one person ahead of you.
Please wait a moment.
Ooh...
is it gonna take long?
I have to take Nine
to a workshop after.
Not at all. It's just gonna be a second.
You can tell me if it does take long,
so I can take him to another clinic.
It's just that we're truly in a rush.
My apologies,
our clinic has
a first-come, first-served policy.
We will take care of it
as soon as possible.
It's okay.
We'll go somewhere else.
If you and Nine are in a hurry,
feel free to go first.
Wan can wait.
I can.
Are you sure?
My boy can wait,
so...
please go ahead, Ms. Sunny.
Uh, then...
Nine, right this way, please.
Ms. Cher, we're really sorry about that.
It's absolutely fine. I understand.
Thank you for your understanding.
We'll take the best care of him.
Please adore him tons.
If you're looking for
a brand presenter,
feel free to reach out.
Of course.
I will pass the message
along to the higher-ups.
Once you arrive,
go ahead inside.
I have to take care
of the contract at the clinic first.
Alright.
Mm.
Oh!
It's in Lat Pla Khao.
Right...
Okay.
Lat Phrao...
Lat Phrao.
Okay, let's go.
He's still not here, Cher?
He's already 15 minutes late.
I'm sorry,
Luang.
You know I don't like
working with latecomers, right?
Yes, I do.
I am so sorry.
I'm sorry, Cher,
for being late.
I went to the wrong location.
I misheard "Lat Pla Khao"
as "Lat Phrao."
Why didn't you check the maps, Wan?
I'm really sorry.
It's all my fault.
I...
I was gonna check them
when I got close.
Alright.
Forget it.
Go rush inside now.
Hey, wait.
You're really late right now.
If they ask
why you were late,
tell them you got lost.
Yes.
Don't tell anyone about the clinic,
got it?
Got it.
Take one of the straps out.
Go, run along.
- Okay.
- Go.
Hello.
I'm here.
I'm sorry,
it's just that...
I got lost.
Wan, put away
your backpack and come sit.
Okay.
Come on now, we're already late.
There.
Sit next to Nine.
Pleasure to work with you.
Uh...
So...
I'm so happy that
I get to work with you, Nine.
I'm your fan.
I like you very much.
Uh...
Thank you.
Still smiling
after wasting everyone's time?
Can we finally get started, Luang?
Okay,
I'm Luang,
an acting coach.
And this is Pai,
our director.
- Hello.
So, the purpose of our class today
for everyone to grasp
the characters together
because we're filming the pilot soon.
We have so little time left.
Right,
anyone finished the novel?
I have read both the novel and the script.
I have also read
both the novel and the script.
I've only read the script.
It's okay.
Well...
I...
I've read a little bit of the script.
I bought the novel already,
but...
I haven't read it.
Mm...
It's alright, then.
I'll have Nine
volunteer to tell us the story
so that Wan can listen to it, too.
- Alright?
- Sure thing.
Wan probably won't have time to read it.
Okay, so...
So 'The Deep Between Us'
is a love quadrangle
among university students
who are competitive swimmers.
[The Deep Between Us]
Noel
is a sickly young man
who enters a sports university
to pursue his dream.
Oh!
Whoa!
And that's where he meets Copter,
a rising star athlete who's out of form
because of some problems from the past.
That brings them closer together
until they eventually fall in love,
until Sky,
who shares a bitter history with Copter,
comes to test their love.
Meanwhile,
Heart also becomes
an intimidating competition for Copter,
both in sports
and love.
I... like you.
Can I teach you how to swim
instead of Copter?
From what I've heard from Nine,
I think this series
sounds like so much fun.
Uh...
But...
Luang, I have a question.
Right.
What is it?
So...
considering how long the lines are,
well...
how do I memorize them all?
Well...
as an actor,
you just need to figure it out.
So what if...
I couldn't memorize
them no matter how hard I tried?
You need to do your homework then.
Right?
Because if you're prepared,
you're definitely gonna get it.
Uh...
Uh, and...
So...
What do I do with the acting?
Do I look at the camera,
or is there someone
I have to keep an eye on?
Where do my hands go,
or where do I...
Right, okay.
Okay...
Wan, Renji,
you're both new to this, yes?
- Yes.
It's alright.
Then, I'll have Third and Nine
demonstrate it for you.
So...
is there anything to keep an eye on?
There was an accident
with Wan at the clinic,
so he was late to the workshop.
You have to manage
the schedule properly.
I asked you to take care of him,
and that was
the first time everyone met him.
Right,
I'm sorry, Wut.
You do know
that I trust you
when it comes to work, right?
I do.
I'm sorry, sister.
I made your boy run late.
Do you want me to tell Wut
that he was late because I was there?
Fucking nosy!
Oh,
I'm sorry, sister.
The voice in my head got too loud.
Wan has such a familiar face, though.
Have you heard about Nine's stalker?
What are you talking about?
Oops,
but you don't seem to be "S-T-P."
Look who's "crushing" it with their words.
They ended up crushing their own brain.
Is your name "Cher" or "Sur"?
Because I'm surprised
by how incredibly fucking "stupid" you are.
Are we crystal clear?
That was no fun.
Relax.
Most importantly,
live in the moment.
If you're ready, raise your hands.
And action.
Hey, new kid.
Why did you drop out?
My name is Noel.
I didn't ask you that.
Then don't call me "new kid."
Okay, Noel.
Why did you drop out?
Because...
I wanna be a swimming athlete here.
You really wanna swim that much?
Sorry.
Whoa, are you okay?
I am...
Thanks.
Can you even get in the pool?
Sure can.
I wanna be a competitive swimmer.
Then, wanna race?
Sure.
I'm not scared of ya.
Here,
I looked it up.
This is how you do it.
Like this.
With straight arms.
Cut.
That's good.
How was it?
Wan, Renji, what do you think?
Well...
they played their parts well.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
That was fun.
Huh?
That was not for fun.
That was for you to see the acting.
How was their acting? What else is there?
Their acting was so good.
As Nine acted,
his eyes had such amazing emotions.
I feel like
I want to root for him to the max.
I wanna know
what was on your mind when you acted?
Alright, listen.
Listen.
Wan,
Renji,
did you two notice
what it was
that Nine and Third did
before acting in the scene?
Concentration?
Yes!
You're on the right track.
Whatever it is you're acting out,
you need to concentrate.
That's crucial.
- Ah...
- Okay?
Oh, okay.
Right, if so,
act for me.
I want to see how you guys look,
along with the script.
Wan, Renji, act for me.
Be active, be active.
Uh...
Luang,
I don't have the lines memorized.
Take the script with you, then.
Thank you.
Actually, I barely have any idea about it,
so let's do it
how we understand it, yeah?
If you're done concentrating
and ready,
raise your hands.
Three,
two,
one,
action.
"Whoa, Heart.
Long time no see. How have you been?"
Hey, do you know how to high-five?
Jeez, of course!
Uh, Pai.
May I try again?
That's not a question, I'd say.
Start over.
But concentrate first.
Take a deep breath.
If you're ready...
And action.
"Whoa, Heart.
Long time no see. How have you been?"
"It's been good.
Ever since I left the club,
I've never seen anyone."
"But why the sad face?"
Uh...
"Everyone's just the same.
I also left the club."
"You left the club?"
"Mm."
"What a shame."
Uh...
The script says "high-pitched voice."
Do I have to speak in a high pitch?
Jeez, just keep it going.
Follow the impulse.
What is "impulse"?
Translate it.
Um...
Well...
"The urges," yeah.
Listen to the urges.
Ah...
Okay.
So do I have to speak in a high pitch?
Is that really important right now, Wan?
Acting
is not about putting on faces
and relying on the emotions on set.
Do you know
why I asked you that question,
especially you,
if you've read the script or the novel?
It's about understanding
the role you're playing,
what attitude they have,
and what background they've lived through.
It's about understanding human nature.
You didn't even read the script!
So how did that turn out?
You haven't got a clue!
The reason you nailed
the audition and made it here today
is that that day,
you played as yourself.
Get the picture?
I don't remember it.
Oh, my...
Dead...
We're dead.
Here's what we’ll do, Wan.
Answer my question:
what is Sky,
the character you play,
so vengeful about?
Answer me that much.
Uh...
I don't know.
I mean...
From what I read in the script earlier,
I don't know why Sky is so vengeful.
Isn't it too nonsensical?
Wan!
Have you ever been in a relationship?
Uh, never.
I haven't finished the question.
Listen!
You're not listening!
If your significant other died,
how would you feel?
I've never had one.
But...
I guess I'd be really sad.
But Copter didn't mean to,
so why does he have to be so vindictive?
I'm not Sky, so I can't figure it out.
That's the thing!
You don't understand a thing!
No matter what he says,
you never get it!
So what are we gonna do now?
Huh?
Do you suppose
we're ever gonna understand Sky?
Uh...
I don't know,
but...
Uh...
now that I'm in a workshop,
do I have an acting coach?
Fine.
You want an acting coach?
Then, what do you call these butts
sitting in this room?
Uh...
acting coaches.
Get some sleep, Wan.
For tomorrow's schedule,
you're doing a photo shoot
since there's
a book launch event next Monday.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I sucked big time today.
Here.
Take a sip to freshen up.
This is just the first day,
and we did our best.
Who's ever become
a master on their first day?
Let's take a photo,
a Day 1 keepsake.
Wan,
can I take a photo with you, too?
Come on.
Uh...
Can we do another one?
It's just that
the lighting falls onto my face.
Oh, sure.
Okay.
Okay, so...
Post the picture and tag me.
I wanna share the photo I took with you.
Sure thing.
Okay.
[winawann_ mentioned you in their story]
[nine.nw started following winawann_]
[nine.nw started following rainjiii]
Alright.
So...
Wan and Renji, you can go home now.
Alright.
Nine, you stay.
Yes, Luang.
Without any bias,
I don't think Wan is ready
for a series that's about to start filming.
He seems confused.
He can't act.
Above all else,
he doesn't do his homework.
Um, actually...
I agree with Third.
True.
This is pretty damn hard, Pai.
I'm gonna say this as a director.
I honestly see some potential in Wan,
but I've gotta admit.
It was terrible. He couldn't act at all.
But I think...
he lacks experience
and is still finding
his own way in acting.
Just give him a chance.
It's only been a day.
So people who don't
put in effort deserve a chance?
Third, I have to ask:
why are you so biased against him?
This was his first day,
and he's a rookie.
Doesn't he need time
to adjust or something?
As for all those stupid questions he asked,
I think that's a good thing.
It's good to ask questions
when you're clueless,
and that is
how you put effort into work.
If you think being unprepared is good,
then you do you.
Uh, so...
Could I voice my opinion?
I actually think that
the problem isn't him alone.
Maybe it's also...
some other student in the class?
Well...
the problem is you're
the only one he's looking at.
So that'd mean you're also the problem.
I'm heading out.
Bye, Luang.
- Bye, Pai.
- Bye.
Get home safe.
I actually...
don't agree with Third, guys,
but...
Wan really can't act.
It's gonna be a bit hard, isn't it?
Mm,
that's right.
We still have some time
to change our minds, Pai.
How about this?
I don't wanna run on dictatorship here.
Why don't we go ask North?
Let him settle this.
Mm...
Actually...
it'd be great if we could
quickly talk to North.
Mm.
Right, excuse me.
What's the deal with Renji?
He was as stiff as a board.
The acting wasn't good.
He's the diamond.
And a diamond
is even stiffer than a board.
There is...
shine
in diamonds.
Stiffness, sure.
Do you have a problem
looking at me like that?
I should be the one asking.
Just tell me you don't like me.
Sure,
I don't like you.
I don't like you, either.
I'm not asking you to.
And just so you know,
you're my coworker now.
If you suck, then everyone sucks.
Nine will suck.
And this series will suck.
I don't care why you joined the industry,
but I hate how unprofessional you are.
And if you keep this up,
I can remove you from the project.
What gives you the right?
I have every right.
I can even do it right now.
If you don't value your career,
at least value your bias's work.
You wouldn't wanna
ruin his work, would you?
I don't want to ruin this project.
Third,
Pitch is asking for you at the office.
Both of you.
Come on.
How was the workshop?
It was okay.
There was no problem.
Oh...
except for the new guys.
Why? What about them?
Can they not act?
No, neither one of them can,
especially the boy named Wan.
He was late and...
unprepared.
Okay, I'll bring this to North's attention
because it's affecting our team.
But you two,
this was the first day of the workshop,
yet you don't have
a single photo together.
How was that possible?
If you don't do it,
the series will have no buzz.
And look, the production team said
you should follow every cast member.
Uh...
Nine already did.
I saw it.
Third didn't.
Why the sigh, Third?
Was that all you wanted to say?
How about I go home to prepare
and get some sleep?
This could've been a text.
Boomer...
Ooh.
Uh...
That just sounds like a viral moment.
The timing was perfect.
I... I couldn't miss it.
Mm.
Go...
So we're done here?
I'm heading out.
Oh,
and if you enjoy talking
to my mom so much,
go take care of her.
How long do I have
to put up with this brat's behavior?
Did you see that?
I did.
I was looking...
If he wasn't my star moneymaker...
Calm down.
I'd have kicked him off the building.
Next time,
bring the contract back home to read,
not sign it then and there.
Well, look at the offer he gave me.
I was scared he was gonna change his mind.
I'd be dead, money flushed down the drain.
Well, gotta work hard.
You need 500,000 to settle the debt.
Yeah.
It'll be fine.
As long as I pay it off for Mom,
I'm happy.
Good luck, brother.
I know you can do it.
Just don't breach the contract!
The fee is pretty brutal.
Mm.
Right, View.
Hm?
I wanna transfer Mom 500,000 baht,
but I can't. What do I do?
Ugh, you have to adjust the limit first.
I think the maximum amount is 200,000.
[Nine has started his first day
of workshop for 'The Deep Between Us']
[#Nineepnp
#TheDeepSeries #TheDeepBetweenUs]
[Your post was sent]
Look at you.
Still have the energy to trend the tags?
Aren't you tired?
I'm fine.
Just doing something for someone I love
is enough to make me feel refreshed.
However...
today, your fave
picked a fight with me,
saying that I didn't do my homework
or put in effort.
I was humiliated.
Oh,
was he spitting facts, though?
A little.
I'm still feeling bad.
There, it's a good thing
he chewed you out.
It'd be strange if he didn't.
You can just...
be well-prepared to shut him up.
Remember all your lines
and deliver a spicy performance.
I don't know if I can do it.
You can.
You always can.
Keep it going!
Mm!
I can do it!
Wait, no...
I have to nail it!
Fabulous!
Right, so today...
You saw Nine all day.
Must be heavenly for you, huh?
Yes, I met him
today.
He's so freaking cool!
I've already told him
that I liked him very much,
and that I was his fan!
Ugh!
You're not being smart again!
When you told him you were his fan,
how did he and other people react?
Huh?
Well...
Other people didn't say anything,
but your bias!
Huh?
Stop liking him!
He's mean...
Mean how?
Well, your fave
is absolutely foul-mouthed.
Well, he's a red-flag top,
mysterious and intimidating,
almost like he could devour a whole person.
Though with only a single smile,
he drops his act and becomes a pug!
How cute!
Ugh!
Stop flying over the moon.
[third.tharit started following you]
Hey!
Right.
I told you he was gonna go, "Woof, woof"!
"Woof," you daughter of a gun.
We have the same parents.
Ooh!
You followed him back. I caught that!
Do you see him
as an idol or a boyfriend?
What are you saying? Not getting it.
Oops...
why did you trip on my leg? That hurt.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Bring it on!
Aw, you just shrank into a baby.
So a boyfriend vibe, for sure!
[The Deep Between Us]
Look at that.
They're so squeezed together.
Mm, true.
But I've been in their place before.
No matter how squeezed you are,
as long as you can meet someone you love,
you're willing to do it all.
So why do they not arrange proper seats?
Maybe the space is too small.
I've seen this at so many events.
Strange.
Nine!
Nine!!
- Ooh?
- Whoa?
Hey...
Got any inhaler? Somebody passed out.
Oh, my.
Somebody just passed out.
Move, move, move.
Where are the staff?
Third,
don't.
Excuse me, coming through!
Wan!!
Coming through.
Wan...
Someone just passed out, Cher.
Just... Just a second.
Miss.
Miss...
How are you holding up?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry...
If you want it to go away,
listen to me.
Try this method.
Miss,
look right here.
Blow on my finger.
Think of it as a flower.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Hold your breath.
One...
Two...
Keep doing it.
Smell the flower,
and slowly hold your breath.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
Wan.
Let's go.
The staff will take it from here.
- Let's go.
- Alright.
Let's get you back on the stage.
♫But I'm ready to leave it all behind♫
♫Just so I could trade it for the sky♫
♫Even though it pains,♫
♫Even though the trace of tears remains,♫
♫No pain, no gain, no pain, no gain♫
♫Even though it's a long way to the end♫
♫I'm ready to leave it all behind♫
♫Just so I could claim the sky♫
♫I'd sacrifice my being♫
♫Without looking back and regretting♫
♫No pain, no gain, no pain, no gain♫
♫For the end I yearn for in my veins♫
♫I'm hell-bent on moving heaven and earth♫
[Wan's not a good fit for Sky; he's too playful
and slender for how I imagined Sky
It's Nine's first leading role we've waited
for so long; don't just back the newcomer]
Miss.
[I'm taking back what I said
I'm sorry, Wan, your look today is so Sky
you're the only one who helped the fan]
Look right here.
Blow on my finger.
[The boy named Wan won my heart today
while everyone else stood still]
[The boy's name is Wan, right?
May he flourish]
[Don't know a single one of them,
but I remember Wan now]
[I'm just wondering about the whole thing;
did no one think to do anything?]
Think of it as a flower.
[I'm a Nine stan but kinda disappointed
that he just stood and watched]
That boy, Wan,
is becoming more popular
than Third and Nine now.
If there's anything
I can do to hinder him,
I'll do it, okay?
This is like...
I'm just an extra.
If you don't want to, then don't.
Who are you even playing?
We're photographing Sky.
When will you stop being so stupid?
If you don't like me, leave me alone.
You're pretending to hate me,
but you actually like me, right?
What the heck are you doing?
Can't you just play along? I want to keep going.
Maybe it's because I had to do it with you...
That's why I don't feel like it.
♫To reach the summit,
the more I climb, the colder♫
♫The closer I get to seizing it, the lonelier♫
♫Just like a star so bright,♫
♫The further from the dark nights,♫
♫The more ablaze, primed to burn down♫
♫Just like how I lost touch
with people along the way,♫
♫The more steps I took,
the more desolate I became♫
♫As though I'm cursed in my soul♫
♫So deeply, I wound everyone
who makes me whole♫
♫No one's heart♫
♫Do I want to tear apart♫
♫By my own hands♫
♫But I'm ready to leave it all behind♫
♫Just so I could trade it for the sky♫
♫Even though it pains,♫
♫Even though the trace of tears remains,♫
♫No pain, no gain, no pain, no gain♫
♫Even though it's a long way to the end♫
♫I'm ready to leave it all behind♫
♫Just so I could claim the sky♫
♫I'd sacrifice my being♫
♫Without looking back and regretting♫
♫No pain, no gain, no pain, no gain♫
♫For the end I yearn for in my veins♫
♫I'm hell-bent on moving heaven and earth♫
[Mr. Fanboy Series]